// Turkce Ceviri: mertpivvo - by mertpivvo
"lang" 
{ 
"Language" "English" 
"Tokens" 
{
"EYECyber_titleLabel"		" "
	
"EYECyber_subTitleLabel"	" "

"EYECyber_brouzoufLabel"	"Brouzouf"
"EYECyber_descriptionLabel"	"İmplant"
"EYECyber_costLabel" 		"Yükseltme\nMaliyeti"
"EYECyber_levelLabel"		"Sv"
"EYECyber_upLabel"		"Yükselt"

"EYECyber_CyberBrainLabel"	"Siber Beyin"

"EYECyber_CyberEyeLabel"	"Siber Gözler"

"EYECyber_CyberArmLabel"	"Siber Kollar"

"EYECyber_AdrenalineLabel"	"Adrenalin\nEnjektörü"

"EYECyber_CyberWeaponLabel"	"Siber Silah\nArayüzü"

"EYECyber_ResurectorLabel"	"Sinirsel Kontrol"

"EYECyber_CyberNeuronalLabel"	"Siber Nöral\nArayüz"

"EYECyber_CyberSkullLabel"	"Siber Zırhlı\nKafatası"

"EYECyber_PsyDecuplatorLabel"	"Psiyonik Yükseltici"

"EYECyber_MuscularControlLabel"	"Kas Kontrolü"

"EYECyber_CyberTorsoLabel"	"Siber Zırhlı\nGövde"

"EYECyber_FireWallLabel"	"Güvenlik Duvarı"

"EYECyber_WiredReflexLabel"	"Kablolu Refleksler"

"EYECyber_CyberLegLabel"	"Siber Bacaklar"

"EYECyber_CyberBrainSum"	"Zihinsel Stabiliteyi Artırır\nHacklemeyi Artırır\nİlkyardımı Artırır\nRefleksi Artırır\0"
"EYECyber_CyberEyeSum"		"Flaş etkilerini azaltır\nTermal görüş siber yeteneğini artırır\0"
"EYECyber_CyberArmSum"		"Gücü artırır\nKol zırhını güçlendirir\0"
"EYECyber_AdrenalineSum"	"Dayanıklılığı artırır\0"
"EYECyber_CyberWeaponSum"	"İsabeti artırır\0"
"EYECyber_ResurectorSum"	"Direnç Modları"
"EYECyber_CyberNeuronalSum"	"Hacking Artır\0"
"EYECyber_CyberSkullSum"	"Baş zırhını güçlendir\0"
"EYECyber_PsyDecuplatorSum"	"Psionics Artır\0"
"EYECyber_MuscularControlSum"	"Güç Artır\0"
"EYECyber_CyberTorsoSum"	"Gövde zırhını güçlendir\0"
"EYECyber_FireWallSum"		"Hacking Savunmasını Artır\0"
"EYECyber_WiredReflexSum"	"Reaksiyonu Artır\nÇevikliği artır\0"
"EYECyber_CyberLegSum"		"Çevikliği Artır\nBacak zırhını güçlendir\0"

"EYECyber_CyberBrain"
"This upgrade increases the user's mental processing capabilities, improving hacking skills, reflexes, and mental stability. By using a variety of neural systems integrated into different parts of the brain, the efficiency of simple cognitive tasks and memory retention are enhanced.\n\nReaction : +%s1\nHCK : +%s4\nMST : +%s3\nMED : +%s2\n\nTriangulator Range : %s5\nDecreases energy consumed by related implants."

"EYECyber_CyberEye"
"The user's eyes are completely replaced with ocular implants, which are enhanced with complex systems that help improve accuracy with firearms. The upgrade also makes it possible to install additional implants, such as E.Y.E. Vision.\n\nACC : +%s2\n\nCloak energy consumption : -%s3\nCyber Wave Range: %s1\nEnables use of EYE vision\nIncreases detection time of sensory waves.\nDecreases energy consumed by related implants."

"EYECyber_CyberArm"
"This upgrade replaces the user's arms with artificial limbs made from a hybrid of sythentic alloys and artificial muscles. These limbs imbue the user with amplified physical strength and protection, while energy use is regulated by integrated microchips.\n\nSTR : +%s1\n\nArm Protection : +%s2\nDecreases energy consumed by related implants."

"EYECyber_Adrenaline"
"An artificial pump that generates high reserves of adrenaline, which is injected directly into the bloodstream. This boost in adrenaline enhances the user's regeneration abilities, increasing the rate at which HP and Energy recover. \n\nEND : +%s1\n\nIncreases energy recovery rate.\nDecreases energy consumed by related implants."

"EYECyber_CyberWeapon"
"An array of microprocessors are embedded into the user's brain and nervous system, enhancing hand-eye coordination. This heightened connection between mind and body improves accuracy with all firearms. Users with the Fire Control System installed benefit from additional recoil reduction.\n\nACC : +%s1\n\nFire Control bonus : +%s2\nDecreases energy consumed by related implants."

"EYECyber_Resurector"
"This upgrade raises the amount of Resurrect Modules available to the user by one. It also helps reduce all types of physical and mental fatigue."

"EYECyber_CyberNeuronal"
"A microprocessor is implanted into the brain, improving the user's hacking abilities. The implant also stimulates the mitochondria within cells to replicate exponentially. This increases the energy gained and decreases the health drained when used in harmony with the Life Tap implant.\n\nHCK : +%s1\n\nLife Tap Energy Gain : %s2\nLife Tap Health Drain : %s3\nDecreases energy consumed by related implants.\nUpgrades dermal plating."

"EYECyber_CyberSkull"
"This upgrade replaces segments of the skull with titanium alloy plates that provide optimal protection against brain damage. Also incorporated is a biotech chip that stimulates the thyroid, improving its ability to regulate and decrease radiation.\n\nHead Protection : +%s1"

"EYECyber_PsyDecuplator"
"A cerebral implant that redirects the path of energy generated by the body, which increases the force of Psionic attacks. Defense against Psionic attacks is also increased.\n\nPsionic Damage : +%s1\nPsionic Defense : +%s2"

"EYECyber_MuscularControl"
"Carbon-reinforced muscle fibers developed in vitro are woven into the body's natural muscles. This combination of synthetic and organic muscle fibers improves the user's overall strength.\n\nSTR : +%s1"

"EYECyber_CyberTorso"
"This titanium alloy torso replacement protects against all types of damage to the Upper and Lower torso. Also included is a complete suite of biological protection systems, from toxin filtration systems to protection against organ failure.\n\nUpper and Lower Torso Protection : +%s1"

"EYECyber_FireWall"
"This upgrade utilizes hardware and firmware modifcations that monitor and process all cyber brain network traffic. The user's offensive hacking abilities are enhanced, as well as the brain's defense against incoming hacks.\n\nOffensive Hacking : %s2\nDefensive Hacking : %s1\nAllow counter-attack by virus."

"EYECyber_WiredReflex"
"A complex series of circuitry and neuro-transmitters that replace the nervous system give the user enhanced reflexes and motor control.\n\nReaction: +%s1\nAGI : +%s2"

"EYECyber_CyberLeg"
"The legs are replaced with forged cybernetic replacements, giving the user superhuman athletic abilities. Both sprint speed and jump height are improved, and injuries sustained from falling are diminished. A series of motors in the feet decrease the amount of noise made while moving.\n\nMovement Speed : +%s2\nLeg Protection : +%s3\nSprint Boost : x%s4\nJump Boost : x%s5\nFootfall sound reduction : %s1"


"EYECyber_CyberRevo"	"Bir sonraki seviyeye yükseltmek için gerekli araştırmaya ihtiyacın var."
"EYECyber_Cybermancie"	"Bir sonraki seviyeye yükseltmek için gerekli araştırmaya ihtiyacın var."
"EYECyber_CyberNecro"	"Bir sonraki seviyeye yükseltmek için gerekli araştırmaya ihtiyacın var."
"EYECyber_MaxLevel"	"Maksimum Seviyeye Ulaşıldı"
} 
}  
